let's look at how to make this logo a
让我们来看看如何使这个徽标成为
convenient way to do this is to use the
要做到这一点，方便的方法是使用
power stroke
动力冲程
it wasn't until Illustrator CS6 that you
直到Illustrator CS6，你才发现
were able to create a variable stroke
我们能够创建可变的笔划
width
宽度
it's a powerful tool to have in your
这是一个强大的工具，在您的
Arsenal so let's have a look
阿森纳，让我们来看看
select the ellipse tool and drag a
选择椭圆工具，然后将一个
circle
圆
[Music]
[音乐]
I will make the start and end points fit
我会让起点和终点都合适
the large Arc
大弧度
I go to pathfx and choose power stroke
我转到pathfx，选择了POWER SHOCK
I want the start and end cap to be
我想要开始和结束的上限是
rounded
舍入
I drag the purple control point to
我将紫色控制点拖动到
adjust the width
调整宽度
I lower the opacity so I can clearly see
我降低了不透明度，这样我就可以清楚地看到
both shapes
两种形状
[Music]
[音乐]
I zoom in on the start point
我放大起点
I fine tune the end point
我微调了终点
at this moment I have three points to
此时此刻，我有三点要做
adjust the line width
调整线条宽度
but you can remove and add points
但您可以删除和添加点数
to add a control point I control click
要添加我控制的控制点，请单击
on a purple diamond
在一颗紫色钻石上
now I have four points to control the
现在我有四个点来控制
line with
与……保持一致
I will create a fifth control Point by
我将通过以下方式创建第五个控制点
control clicking on a purple diamond
Ctrl键点击紫色钻石
to make the top curve I duplicate the
为了制作顶部曲线，我复制了
large Arc
大圆弧
I will reposition the start and end
我将重新定位起点和终点
points
支点
I see I must rotate the arc somewhat
我知道我必须稍微旋转一下弧线
so I press the space bar
所以我按了空格键
I will have to rotate a bit more but
我将不得不再旋转一点，但是
this time I will reposition the rotation
这一次我将重新定位旋转
point
点
I'll save my paths so I can adjust them
我会保存我的路径，这样我就可以调整它们
later if needed so I duplicate them I
以后如果需要，我会复制它们
hide the original shapes that have the
隐藏具有
live path effects then I will turn the
活动路径效果，然后我将把
duplicates into regular paths and unite
复制到规则路径并合并
them
他们
now let's color the path
现在让我们给这条小路上色
I go to fill and stroke and select
我去填充和描边，然后选择
radial gradient
径向渐变
I select the gradient tool and move the
我选择渐变工具并将
gradient to the bottom left
渐变到左下角
I click on the dropper tool and Sample
我点击Dropper工具和示例
the green and for the outside color I
绿色，外面的颜色是
sample the blue I shift Ctrl drag to
采样蓝色的I Shift Ctrl拖动到
make the gradient bigger now let's place
让渐变变得更大，现在让我们
the text
文本
I will use assistant which is a free
我会用免费的助手
Google font
Google字体
I click on spacing and set spacing
我点击间距并设置间距
between letter to 15.
在字母到15之间。
I want to remove the horizontal stroke
我想去掉水平笔划
from the letter A
从字母A开始
to do this I go to path object to path
为此，我转到路径对象到路径
I select the node tool and drag over the
我选择节点工具并在
horizontal stroke
水平行程
I press delete
我按删除键